Garrison Family Papers, 1694-2005 (bulk 1830-1950)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES X. STEPHENSON FAMILY (1818-1973), 1.75 linear ft.
  Edith Stephenson married WLG (1874) in 1906. This series contains correspondence, memorabilia, diaries, and writings of the Stephenson family dating back to the early 1800s. The authors include Edith's parents, Benjamin Turner and Lucinda ("Luda") Grant Stephenson, and her brothers and sisters. This series contains two subseries: Biographical material and memorabilia and Correspondence. Both are arranged alphabetically by person. There is a Benjamin Turner Stephensons in three generations. Each of them is identified by his birth date.
  The first subseries consists of genealogical material, two diaries (1870, 1892-1916), and school compositions (1868, n.d.) of Lucinda ("Luda") Grant Stephenson); financial, official and miscellaneous documents; and memorabilia.
  The second subseries, Correspondence, consists of Stephenson family letters, with the exception of Edith Stephenson Garrison whose correspondence is with that of the Garrison family. All letters are outgoing unless specified otherwise. Although there is some business correspondence and a small amount between family members, including courtship letters from Luda Grant to Benjamin Stephenson (1869-71). Most of the correspondence is written to Edith and WLG (1874) from Edith's parents and siblings. Benjamin Turner Stephenson (1886) was an artist, and included in an 1898 letter to Edith is a set of paper dolls. There is also a substantial number of letters from Walter Stephenson to Edith and WLG (1838) (1915-43) and David Lloyd Garrison (1918-49). The latter includes a scrapbook "file of letters together with enclosures, clippings of writings of Lucien Price and some others" (1927-29). Although it has not been possible to find him on the Stephenson family tree, it is assumed that he is a Stephenson cousin.
  Photographs of the Stephenson family are located in SERIES VII. PHOTOGRAPHS.
- SERIES XI. SCRAPBOOKS 1833-1908, 4 linear ft.
  There are eighteen scrapbooks belonging Agnes Garrison, George Thompson Garrison, and WLG (1838). These contain clippings, memorabilia, correspondence, and miscellaneous printed material on a variety of subjects. Agnes's two scrapbooks (1870s-1901) contain memorabilia and primarily travel related items. Of the four scrapbooks which belonged to George, of particular interest is his "Record of the 55th Massachusetts Infantry (1868) in which George served as second lieutenant. The remaining eleven scrapbooks (1856-1908) were compiled by WLG (1838). These contain correspondence, his writings and clippings, and information related to his business ventures. Among the topics covered are football, fraternities, anti-imperialism, racial discrimination, and suffrage. Much of this material may be duplicated elsewhere in SERIES IV. WRITINGS AND SPEECHES and SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES.
- SERIES XII. ARTIFACTS 1833-1914
  This series contains fourteen items. Some are boxed with the collection while others are located in the Sophia Smith Collection reading room and the Smith College Museum of Art. One item, an ivory handled cane engraved for WLG (1838) and Ellen Wright Garrison's 40th wedding anniversary is located in the Flat File. Of interest in this series is a silk antislavery banner painted by Josiah Wolcott in the 1840s, a silver cup presented to WLG (1805) by abolitionists (1833), an engraved inkwell belonging to Ellen Wright Garrison, a statue by John Rogers entitled "The Fugitive's Story," and a statue of WLG (1805) by Anne Whitney.
- SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS 1830-2005
  - Papers
    - Boston Public Library 1898-1916, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Harvard University 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Massachusetts Historical Society 1911-17, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous 1891-1968, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Genealogy
    - Family trees 1962-80, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Wendell Phillips Garrison: notes and correspondence 1884 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous notes and correspondence 1880-1962, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Garrison family
    - Bell, Helen Villard 1897 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Benson family 1872, 1946, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bliss, Edith Garrison 1931, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Chubb, Marion Knight Garrison 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Emerson
      - Claire Garrison 1903, n.d (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Robert 1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Agnes 1866-1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Garrison
      - Alice O'Reillyundated (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Annie McKim 1893-94 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Catherine Cooper 1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - David Lloyd 1922-2003, undated, [See also SERIES IV. WRITINGS AND SPEECHES - David Lloyd Garrison - "Tramp Abroad, 1942-1945" and "Early and Late"] (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Edith Stephenson
        - Medical information 1902-50 (Box 1, Folder 19)
        - Will and miscellaneous printed material 1914-74, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Eleanor 1912-62, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Ellen Wright
        - Marriage certificate and miscellaneous material 1864-1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - Verse to Ellen 1878-79, [See also SERIES IV. WRITINGS AND SPEECHES - WLG (1838) - Verses to Ellen] (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - Wills 1908-22 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Francis Jackson 1882-1917 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Frank Wright 1871-75 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - George 1955-70 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Helen Benson 1876 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - James Holley 1954 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Jane Wilson 1937 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - John Bright 1928-42, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Lloyd Kirkham 1932-65, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Lloyd McKim 1900 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Lucy McKim
        - Lucy McKim Garrison, American Musician by Dena Epstein: pamphlet and related material 1887-1973, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
        - Miscellaneous 1864-77, 1925, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Marian Knight 1962 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Ritchie 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Robert Hale 1968, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Theresa Holmes 1915 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Wendell Holmes 1894, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Wendell Phillips
        - Clippings and articles 1905-35, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
        - Letters and Memorials of Wendell Phillips Garrison 1908-09
          - Published book
          - Related material 1908-09 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - "The Vigil" 1907 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        - Will 1901 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - William Lloyd (1805), [See also SERIES IV. WRITINGS AND SPEECHES - WLG (1838) -Tributes]
        - Biographies
          - List by WLG (1838) (Box 3, Folder 1)
          - Published
            - Chapman, John Jay, William Lloyd Garrison 1913
            - Cook, Frances E. An American Hero. The Story of William Lloyd Garrison 1888
            - Crosby, Ernest, Garrison the Non Resistant 1905
            - Garrison, Wendell Phillips, William Lloyd Garrison, 1805-1879; the story of his life told by his children1894, [4v on shelf]
              - Correspondence 1880-93, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
              - Notes and miscellaneous printed material 1880-94 (Box 3, Folder 3)
            - Grimké, Archibald Henry, William Lloyd Garrison: The Abolitionist 1891
            - Smith, Goldwin, The Moral Crusader: A Biographical essay founded on "The story of Garrison's life as told by his children" 1892
            - Tchertkoff, V. G. (Vladimir Grigorevich Chertov) and F. -Holah, A Short Biography of William Lloyd Garrison, With an introductory appreciation of his life and work by Leo Tolstoy 1904
            - Villard, Fanny Garrison, William Lloyd Garrison On Non-Resistance, together with a personal sketch by his daughter, Fanny Garrison Villard, and a tribute to Leo Tolstoy 1924
          - Memoirs and reminiscences
            - Howitt, Mary, "Memoir of William Lloyd Garrison" 1846-47 (Box 4, Folder 1)
            - Norton, Garrison, "And I Will Be Heard" 1962 (Box 4, Folder 2)
            - Garrison, William Lloyd (1838): memoir about his father 1844-45 (Box 4, Folder 3)
            - Mob of 18351835-1885 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        - Tributes and testimonials, [See also SERIES III. CORRESPONDENCE - Letters to the Garrisons - Condolence letters]
          - Public Breakfast 1867 (Box 4, Folder 5)
          - National testimonial 1867 (Box 4, Folder 6)
          - Obituaries 1879 (Box 4, Folder 7)
          - Eulogy and funeral service, 1879
            - Texts and program (Box 4, Folder 8)
            - Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 9)
          - Miscellaneous tributes 1879 (Box 4, Folder 10)
          - Memorials, statues, and portraits 1886-1968, [See also SERIES VII. PHOTOGRAPHS - Anne Whitney statue] (Box 4, Folder 11)
          - Anniversaries
            - 100th, 1905
              - Programs and addresses (Box 4, Folder 12)
              - Clippings and articles
                - English (Box 4, Folder 13-14)
                - German (Box 5, Folder 1)
            - 115th 1910 (Box 5, Folder 2)
            - 200th2005 (Box 5, Folder 2a)
        - Trial for libel of Francis Todd 1830-47 (Box 5, Folder 3)
        - Printed materials, [See also Friends and associates -Blackwell, Alice Stone]
          - Articles 1879-1931, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
          - Clippings 1831-1966, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
          - Pamphlets 1879-1940 (Box 5, Folder 6)
          - Miscellaneous 1836-67, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - William Lloyd (1838)
        - Clippings 1889-1931, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
        - Letters of recommendation 1862-63 (Box 5, Folder 9)
        - Reminiscences dictated to Agnes Garrison 1909 (Box 5, Folder 10)
        - Revere Railroad accident: correspondence
          - Family 1871 (Box 5, Folder 11)
          - Friends 1871 (Box 5, Folder 12)
        - Tributes and testimonials
          - Memorial meetings 1909-10 (Box 5, Folder 13)
          - "Memorial tributes" (bound scrapbook) 1909 (Box 5)
          - Obituaries 1909 (Box 6, Folder 1)
          - Verse 1879-1929, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
          - "Personal tributes, poems, miscellaneous" (collected scrapbook of clippings and articles) 1895-1905 (Box 6, Folder 3)
        - Will 1908 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - William Lloyd (1874)
        - Articles and clippings 1893-1930 (Box 6, Folder 5)
        - Funeral service 1964 (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - Letters of recommendation 1897-1926 (Box 6, Folder 7)
        - Medical information 1892-52, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
        - Will and power of attorney 1929-53 (Box 6, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous 1916-64, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - William Lloyd (1902) 1947-60, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Gould, James 1964-71 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Harwood, Faith Garrison 1910 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Norton
      - Charles Dyer 1910-2010 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Charles McKimundated (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Garrison 1946, 1965, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Katherine Garrison 1943 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Phoutrides
      - Aristides 1915-23 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Margaret Garrison 1956-59, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Platov, Mariquita Villardundated (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Valentine
      - Alan 1935-50, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Lucia Garrisonundated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Villard
      - Fanny Garrison 1906-28, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Henry 1896-1971, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Henry H. 1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Henry Serrano 1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Julia B. Sanford 1903, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Mariquita Serrano 1897, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Mary St. Johnundated (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Oswald Garrison 1923-59, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Oswald Garrison, Jr. 1949-56, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Friends and associates
    - Andrew, John A. 1861-66 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Anthony, John Gould 1877 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Anthony, Susan B. 1868-1906, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Baldwin, William Henry 1905 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Barrows, Isabel C. 1896, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Berenson, Bernard 1934 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Binger, Carl 1964 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Birney, Fitzhugh 1866 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Blackwell
      - Alice Stone 1903-50, undated, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES -Alice Stone Blackwell Fund and SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Suffrage - National American Woman Suffrage Association] (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Henry Brown 1909 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Katherine B.undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Boutwell, George Sewall 1905-08, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Boyd, William Riley 1905-08, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Breshkofskaya, Katherine 1904-25, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Brooks, Phillips 1892-93 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Brown
      - Hallie G.undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - Henry "Box," undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - John 1859-97, 1936, undated, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Abolition - Pamphlets] (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Browning, Robertundated (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Buffum family 1887, 1904 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Butler, Josephine 1907 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Carpenter, Alice 1912 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Chace
      - Elizabeth Buffumundated, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Abolition - Anti-slavery reminiscences] (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - L. G. 1876 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Channing, William Ellery 1842, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Abolition - Pamphlets] (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Chapman, Maria Weston 1840-86, undated, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Abolition-Report to the Ladies of Scotland] (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Chase
      - Donald A. 1938-40, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Richard and William Beverly 1876 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Cheney, Ednah Dow 1905 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Chesson, Frederick W. 1888, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Child, Lydia Maria 1880, [See also Sewall, Harriet Winslow; and SERIES IX. WRIGHT FAMILY - Biographical materials - Mott, Lucretia Coffin, and SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Abolition - Pamphlets and books] (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Clark
      - Alice 1934 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Helen Priestman Bright 1900-27 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Dr. Hilda 1955-63 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - John Bright 1904-33 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Roger 1899-1961 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - William Stephens 1925 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous family 1909, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Clarke, James Freeman: James Freeman Clarke: Autobiography, Diary and Correspondence, edited by Edward Everett Hale 1891
    - Clothier, Esther Clark 1935, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Cockerell, Sir Sydney John 1945-62 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Coffin, Winthropundated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Collins, Rebecca 1909 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Colman, Lucy N. 1890-91, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Conant, Lucy 1887, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Crosby, Ernest Howard 1897-1907 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Cutler, Elbridge J.undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Daniel
      - Charles 1872, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Kate 1858 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Daniels, Mabel 1961 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Davis, Charles 1936-46 undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Diaz, Abby Mortonundated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Douglass Frederick 1846-1947, 1962, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES -Abolition - Pamphlets] (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Du Bois W.E. Burghardt 1915, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Duncan, James 1890 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Emerson, Ralph Waldo 1883-1903, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - FarquharsonMay, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Fawcett, Millicent Garrettundated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Folger family 1939, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Follen, Charles, [See May, Samuel L.]
    - Foster, Abby Kelley 1887 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Fowlds, George W. 1899-1936, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Fowler, Frances 1941-44, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Fowler, Rev. Henryundated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Fry, Elizabethundated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Gale, Philip Bartlett 1945, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - George, Henry 1894-1939, undated, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES-Single tax, and SERIES IV. WRITINGS AND SPEECHES-WLG (1838)- Tributes] (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Gillette, Margaret Clarkeundated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Goode, Edith J. 1970 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Greeley, Horace 1872 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Hartshorne, Rev. T.C 1864, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Hastings, Dr. Caroline 1895 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Henry, Aliceundated (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth 1856-1911 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Hoffman, Gertrude Wesselhoeft 1968 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Holmes, Oliver Wendell 1855, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Howe, Julia Ward 1909 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Huntington, Frederic Dan 1858 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Ingersoll, Ebon C. 1879 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Jackson, Francis 1845-68, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES- Jackson Homestead] (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Jacobs, Sophia Yarnall 1959-62 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Jefferson, Joseph 1883 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Johnson
      - Andrew 1864 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Miriam B. 1881 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Samuel 1854-82 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Tom L. 1899-1910, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Joshi, Anandibai 1927 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Julian, George W. 1851 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Karolyi, Countess 1925 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Kennedy, Mildred, [See SERIES III: CORRESPONDENCE - Correspondence to the Garrisons-Brown, Florence]
    - Kiefer, Daniel 1923 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Kindleberger, Charles P. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Kittredge, Henry Crocker 1967 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Kropotkin, Prince 1899 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Lee, Robert Wardenundated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Lord, Alice Kirkham 1908-39 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Lummis, Dr. Charles Fletcher 1957-64 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - MacKaye
      - Marion Morse and Percy 1913-59 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Percy 1932 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - McKim
      - Charles Follen 1909 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - James Miller 1831-1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Sarah Allibone Speakman 1831-91 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous family 1874-79, 1930-34 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - McLaren, Priscilla Bright 1906 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - MacVeagh, Wayne 1901 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Martineau, Harriet, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Abolition - Pamphlets and SERIES VII. PHOTOGRAPHS -Ambleside]
      - Articles and pamphlets 1839-84 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Society in America, v.21837
    - Maurer, H. B. 1886-1932, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - May
      - George E. 1925 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - John Joseph 1904 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Rev. Joseph 1918 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Samuel J. 1840-86, undated, [See also Books (page 251) and SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Abolition- Pamphlets] (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Merrill, Frances S. 1897 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Nichol, Johnundated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Pankhurst family 1912-60, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Park, John Edgar 1927 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Parker, Theodore
      - Writings 1853-58, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Frothingham, Octavious Brooks, Theodore Parker: A Biography 1874 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Pastoriza, J.J, [See SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES -Single tax - Houston]
    - Peterson, Roger Tory, [See SERIES IV. WRITINGS AND SPEECHES - David L. Garrison]
    - Phillips
      - Ann 1886 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Wendell, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Abolition- Pamphlets]
        - Articles, miscellaneous printed material and verse 1880-1892, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
        - Statue 1915 (Box 12, Folder 3)
        - Writings and speeches 1859-92 (Box 12, Folder 4)
        - Speeches, Lectures and Letters (letter to Wendell P. Garrison inserted) 1863, 1891
    - Pillsbury, Parker 1867-98, 1922, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Abolition - Pamphlets] (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Post, Louis 1928, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Potter, Bishop 1894 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Price, Lucien ("Uncle Dudley") 1923-45, undated, [See also SERIES X. STEPHENSON FAMILY - Correspondence- Walter Stephenson to David Lloyd Garrison] (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Prang, Louis, n.d (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Purvis, Robert 1898 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Quincy, Edmund 1904 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Robinson, Edward 1895, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Saltonstall, Leverett 1839 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Sayre, Nora 1936-73, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Severance, Carolineundated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Sewall, Harriet Winslow 1880, [See Flat File]
    - Seward Family 1865, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Shaw, Anna Howardundated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Smalley, Evelyn Garnaut 1938 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Smallwood, Rev. John J. 1892-1904, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Gerrit 1862-1906 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Joseph Lindon 1885-97, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Roswellundated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Spence, Catherine H 1839, 1905 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Stafford, Wendell Phillips 1912, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Stanton, Elizabeth Cadycirca 1856, 1902, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Stone, Lucy 1893 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Stowe, Harriet Beecher, [See SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS - WLG (1805)- clippings]
    - Sumner, Charles 1856-72, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - ABOLITION - pamphlets] (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Terry, Ellen 1887, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Thompson
      - George 1840-1913, undated, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Abolition] (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Ruth Brown 1904 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Tolman, Harriet S.undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Tolstoy, Leo 1892-1905, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Tubman, Harriet
      - Clippingsundated (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Bradford, Sarah H., Harriet, The Moses of Her People 1886 (Box 13)
    - Twitchell, Eliza Stowe 1918 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Washington, Booker T. 1895-1908, undated, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Race -Education -Tuskegee Normal and Industrial School] (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Webb, Alfred 1873-1908, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Weld, Theodore Dwight 1883-1909, undated, [See also SERIES V. FINANCIAL MATERIALS -WLG (1874) - Theodore Dwight Weld estate] (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Wells, Ida B. undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Whittier, John Greenleaf 1892-93, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Wilberforce, Williamundated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Wilcox, Ella Wheelerundated (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Wirth, Jacob 1965 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Woodhull, Victoria 1871, [See also SERIES X. WRIGHT FAMILY - Lucretia Coffin Mott writings] (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Wright, Henry C.undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Wright, Teresa 1972 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Zakrzewska, Dr. Marie E. 1857-1902 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- SERIES II. DIARIES 1854-1995
  - Garrison
    - Agnes
      - 1879-86 (Box 14)
      - 1887-1908 (Box 15)
      - 1909-36 (Box 16)
      - 1937-45 (Box 17)
    - David
      - 1950-60 (Box 18)
      - 1961-65 (Box 19)
      - 1966-70 (Box 20)
      - 1971-76 (Box 21)
      - 1977-82 (Box 22)
      - 1983-85 (Box 23)
      - 1986-88 (Box 24)
      - 1989-91 (Box 25)
      - 1992-94 (Box 26)
      - 1995 (Box 27)
      - Indexes (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Notes (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Edith Stephenson
      - Datebooks 1907-22 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
      - Diaries 1898, 1940, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Eleanor 1913-15 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Ellen Wright
      - 1854-56 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - 1857-1912 (Box 29, Folder 1-5)
    - Frank Wright and Mildred Yarnall
      - 1914-29 (Box 30)
      - 1930-45 (Box 31)
      - 1946-61 (Box 32, Folder 1-7)
    - Mildred Yarnall 1886 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Robert Hale